Who's that guy?
Can you still stand?
Y-Yes...
You turn your back to us?
Your head must be empty!
What?
Got you!
Ow!
You dare take aim at me?
How wicked!
This is an elven village, you know.
So long as your mist is dealt with,
there is no target they cannot hit.
Of all the impudent...
What's that?
Finally here, I see.
Melee
Hmph! I'll crush these puny
humans before he gets here!
This mana...
It seems she has arrived, too.
O evil snake that binds my soul...
Feast on my hatred, imbibe my lamentation,
and turn into a seven-headed
harbinger of disaster!
I'm really angry right now!
How could you hurt the
elves and spirits like this!
Jalaam Dualam!
Sod off!
Your mana will feed my mist!
I've been waiting for that.
O laws of power.
Come to me and gather,
and erupt into flames.
Explosion!
Pathetic.
An ugly demonic flower would
do well to know her place.
Quiet, you stupid rose!
Dolan.
You did well, Celina.
I'll take it from here.
Sure.
Heed my words, O laws of earth and fire.
Gather thy hellfire and become
my spear of judgment!
Ignite Pilam!
Not going to let me take
out his friends, huh?
Celina!
You cut a pathetic figure, Geolude.
My name is Gellen.
I seek to duel you, lamia girl.
You are not allowed to refuse.
Huh?
A new foe. But he's not the one
with the aura from before.
Gellen! She's my prey!
Celina!
How can this be?
Christina!
I see.
That, and the power you displayed before,
suggests you're a superhuman.
Superhuman?
This is getting interesting!
You are a worthy opponent to take down!
I'm not sure I understand,
but I'm glad you seem to be enjoying this.
Awaken, El Spada.
Even more amusing!
You're surprisingly slow.
You wounded me this badly?
I'll tear you into a million pieces!
Come at me, you scoundrel!
Halt my target's movements, O earth spirits!
Dolan, let me take him.
Cursed Blast!
Yes!
Way to go.
Such an energetic little girl.
Jalaam Dualam!
This is quite comforting, if anything.
The snakes in the demonic
realm aren't quite so nice.
Go ahead.
Try and strangle me to death!
Not good enough.
Are you not prepared to kill despite
inheriting the curse of the snake?
Is that it?
A half-hearted girl shouldn't be setting
foot in a battle of life and death!
This is war!
No, you don't.
Such power.
This battle is over.
Halt!
There's the fourth and final one.
We've taken out most of the demon
troops to the west of the village.
That only leaves the leaders.
How's it going over there?
Hey, Gio.
Are you listening?
What is with that terrifying mana?
Gellen, I apologize for
butting into your battle.
It matters not.
He's clearly a cut above in terms of power.
Geolude and gang try to torment
you in battle, but not this guy.
He has a combative aura
that's pointed and refined.
He seeks the thrill of
battle above all else.
Not only do you not fear us,
but you also wound us? Impressive.
I have not run into a force like
this on the surface in eons.
This will be entertaining!
Have a taste of this, then!
Oh? You're swift, human.
The name's Dolan! Remember that!
Hm, Dolan? I know of one with that name.
Not that you would be
related to him in any way.
Oho?
What was that?
Did he notice my draconic mana?
Still...
You don't have the time to be taken aback.
Explosion!
Well done.
He blocked Explosion by having his shield
and three swords take the brunt of it.
Wow. He has that demon on the back foot.
Dolan!
Who is that man?
Nice.
I am truly surprised that you
would be so capable, Dolan.
You...
I thought you were a demon
the same as the other three,
but you are clearly a cut above.
Former divinity... Are you a fallen god?
I can scarcely believe that a
human could be that perceptive.
I take it you have somewhat of
a secret identity yourself.
It's not something
I'm willing to share here.
This is bad.
I can't beat him in my human form.
But if I use my draconic powers
to fight him at full strength,
the elven village will be destroyed.
True, we need not speak with our words.
Our swords shall do all the talking.
What's more, as I possess three blades,
they can say a lot more
than my tongue ever could!
A truly splendid opponent!
I didn't step in enough!
Great power that burns my body and soul!
Truly am I fortunate! I never expected
to find this on the surface!
Is he building up his mana?
You can't focus on Georg alone!
Prepare to die, human!
Dolan!
Girlies, you'll have to go through me first.
Die!
I'm not about to give up my life for that,
you demons!
He nullified it with wind?
He blew away my mist so easily?!
Energy Bolt!
Pardon their interruption.
But I trusted that a surprise
attack wouldn't take you down.
Surrender to my strength, heaven.
Yield to me, earth.
Dolan, my inhuman human,
should you stave off this attack,
I'll acknowledge you as
a truly formidable foe.
Behold one of my ultimate moves,
the Three Demonic Light Blades!
Dolan!
Will you block it, evade it, or perish?!
Ooh!
How wonderful!
You cut down my ultimate move
head-on, albeit on the surface?
It was worth taking on that stupid
contract and coming up here.
I hate to rain on your parade,
but I'm not fighting to
entertain you, fallen god.
I've tired of this.
What?
You're worried about the women and children?
You cannot fight me while
avoiding collateral damage.
In that case...
Hear me, forest dwellers!
Will you continue to fight
us until you perish?
Or will you choose to join
our forces and live on?
You are free to choose
from these two options.
We will return to this settlement in
three days' time, army in tow again.
Use that time to debate and discuss,
and decide your future!
Geolude, Gellen, Raflasia,
no more for tonight.
Hear me, weak lamia girl.
Know that showing compassion to your
foes is a greater sin than defeat.
I will not forget the humiliation
I suffered tonight, superhuman!
Sadly, my memory is not quite so good.
I'll make sure to kill you myself.
I'll torment you until you come begging
to be put out of your misery.
No, I'll be avenging my friends and family,
you filthy demonic flower spirit.
Three days from now.
We will show no mercy to anyone then.
Understood.
I promise I'll show you my
full capabilities then.
I never expected to fight him personally.
Fate is a cruel mistress.
Dolan!
Are you okay?
That smile you gave me had
me fearing the worst!
I'm fine.
Nary a scratch on me, as you can see.
Are you two unhurt, though?
I'm fine...
I'm all right, too.
There is a lot I wish to ask you.
Should I save it for later?
I would appreciate that.
Besides, it looks like Gio and the
elves wish to speak with me, too.
Not the warmest of welcomes.
It is what it is. We came at a bad time.
We'll have to gain their
respect with our actions.
Pardon us, Tribal Chief Dio.
Welcome back.
I've received word of the battle.
Gio, are they the ones?
Yes.
I heard you're from Verun Village.
I must thank you for helping Merl, too.
I'm Dio the elf.
This is Vlaic the wolfman and
Alsienne the arachne.
Dolan...
They must be the chiefs of the
various tribes residing in this forest.
I've heard that you possess power
surpassing that of the average human.
Then we must ask for the viewpoint of
one living in a human town, as well.
Headmistress Olivia?!
It's been too long, everyone.
Next Episode
This week's lucky item is El Spada!
Look forward to next time!